Subtitle Provide by dramacool.asia Translator [Admin.@YNG]
تم توفير الترجمة بواسطة مترجم dramacool.asia [Admin.@YNG]
[Between Love and Frost]
[بين الحب والصقيع]
[Episode 14]
[الحلقة 14]
You really want to die?
هل تريد أن تموت حقا؟
Yes, I do.
نعم أفعل.
I never want to see you again.
لا أريد رؤيتك مرة أخرى أبدًا.
Even if I die,
حتى لو مت،
it's better than being humiliated
إنه أفضل من الإذلال
and tortured.
وتعرض للتعذيب.
I told you before
لقد قلت لك من قبل
your life belongs to me.
حياتك ملكي.
I want you alive.
أريدك حياً.
No matter how painful it is,
بغض النظر عن مدى الألم الذي يسببه ذلك،
you will endure it.
سوف تتحملها.
I'm such a person
انا مثل هذا الشخص
that once I set my mind on something,
أنه بمجرد أن أضع عقلي على شيء ما،
no one can hold me back.
لا أحد يستطيع أن يمنعني.
Chu Minghui.
تشو مينغوي.
♪Love is an abyss one cannot escape♪
♪الحب هو الهاوية التي لا يمكن الهروب منها♪
♪The more I doubt, the more I fear♪
كلما زاد شكي، زاد خوفي
How dare you!
كيف تجرؤ!
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Only when I'm dead,
فقط عندما أموت،
can you...
هل يمكنك...
finally set yourself free.
أخيرا حرر نفسك.
♪I hesitate in every word and every moment♪
♪أتردد في كل كلمة وفي كل لحظة♪
Don't...
لا...
let yourself dwell in suffering.
اسمح لنفسك بالبقاء في المعاناة.
♪Flee, and break♪
♪اهرب وانكسر♪
♪The endless shackle of darkness♪
♪قيد الظلام الذي لا نهاية له♪
Chu Minghui!
تشو مينغوي!
You won't die.
لن تموت.
I won't let you die!
لن أدعك تموت!
♪Come to me, my love♪
♪تعالي إليّ يا حبيبتي♪
Someone!
شخص ما!
Come here now!
تعال هنا الآن!
♪No more worries♪
♪لا مزيد من القلق♪
♪There will always be a gap♪
♪سيكون هناك دائمًا فجوة♪
Chu Minghui!
تشو مينغوي!
You must not die!
لا يجب أن تموت!
Absolutely not!
بالتأكيد لا!
[Cunji Hospital of Jiang City]
[مستشفى كونجي بمدينة جيانغ]
♪Let the hatred go♪
♪اترك الكراهية تذهب♪
♪Don't dwell♪
♪لا تتوقف♪
♪Only when flowers wither will scars form♪
♪فقط عندما تذبل الزهور تتشكل الندوب♪
♪Let love and hate scatter with the wind♪
♪دع الحب والكراهية يتناثران مع الريح♪
♪Let myself be free♪
♪أسمح لنفسي أن أكون حرا♪
How is she?
كيف حالها؟
The bullet grazed her heart,
لقد أصابت الرصاصة قلبها،
causing significant damage.
تسبب في أضرار كبيرة.
And she has lost too much blood.
وقد فقدت الكثير من الدم.
You must save her!
يجب عليك انقاذها!
I'm sorry I can't guarantee.
أنا آسف لا أستطيع ضمان ذلك.
Her condition is critical.
حالتها حرجة.
There is not enough blood
لا يوجد ما يكفي من الدم
in our blood bank.
في بنك الدم لدينا.
Take my blood.
خذ دمي.
I've confirmed with the nurse
لقد تأكدت من الممرضة
our blood types match.
فصيلة الدم لدينا تتطابق.
The chances of saving her are very slim.
فرص إنقاذها ضئيلة جدًا.
Save her!
أنقذها!
Take as much as needed.
تناول بقدر الحاجة.
I refuse to give up on her.
أرفض أن أتخلى عنها.
Fine.
بخير.
You haven't repaid what you owe me.
لم تسدد ما عليك من دين لي.
You must survive.
يجب عليك البقاء على قيد الحياة.
I won't allow you to die.
لن اسمح لك بالموت.
[Police Station of Jiang City]
[مركز شرطة مدينة جيانغ]
Mr. Liu,
السيد ليو،
are you satisfied with the prior arrangements?
هل أنت راض عن الترتيبات السابقة؟
I've truly appreciated your gesture,
لقد أقدرت حقا لفتتك،
though the sum falls
على الرغم من أن المبلغ يقع
somewhat short.
قصيرة إلى حد ما.
You've always been scrupulously thorough.
لقد كنت دائمًا دقيقًا وشاملًا.
I know this must be all
أعلم أن هذا يجب أن يكون كل شيء
that you could provide.
التي يمكنك تقديمها.
Thank you for your understanding.
شكرا لتفهمكم.
I hold great faith in your succession as Military Governor,
إنني أؤمن إيمانا كبيرا بخليفتك كحاكم عسكري،
yet you lack that decisive edge now.
لكنك تفتقر إلى تلك الميزة الحاسمة الآن.
Your father left a will at that time,
لقد ترك والدك وصية في ذلك الوقت،
giving all his property to Tongpei.
التبرع بجميع ممتلكاته إلى تونغبي.
But Tongpei
لكن تونغبي
will never share profits with us.
لن يشاركنا الأرباح أبدًا.
So as long as you secure the legacy
طالما أنك تؤمن الإرث
and promise
ووعد
to share with us old men,
لمشاركتنا نحن الرجال المسنين،
I promise to fully support you
أعدك بأنني سأدعمك بشكل كامل
in the succession.
في الخلافة.
Rest assured.
اطمئن، لا تشغل بالك.
A certain associate can resolve that.
يمكن لشريك معين أن يحل ذلك.
Ce.
هذا.
What took you so long?
ما الذي أخذ منك كل هذا الوقت؟
Save me now! Hurry!
أنقذني الآن! أسرع!
Quick!
سريع!
Save me!
أنقذني!
Why are you just standing there?
لماذا تقف هناك فقط؟
Hurry! Save me!
اسرع! انقذني!
You'll be helpful.
سوف تكون مفيدا.
I'm here to rescue you.
أنا هنا لإنقاذك.
How is he?
كيف حاله؟
He is out of immediate danger.
لقد أصبح خارج الخطر المباشر.
I've dressed and treated the wound.
لقد قمت بتغطية الجرح ومعالجته.
The issue is a persistent high fever induced
المشكلة هي ارتفاع مستمر في درجة الحرارة بسبب
by injury infection.
بسبب الإصابة بالعدوى.
He remains unconscious.
ويظل فاقدًا للوعي.
I need him to be conscious urgently.
أحتاجه أن يكون واعيًا بشكل عاجل.
My patience wears thin.
لقد نفذ صبري.
Understood.
مفهومة.
Mr. Song,
السيد سونغ،
let me remind you.
دعني أذكرك.
Keep your mouth sealed.
احفظ فمك مغلقا.
Focus on your duties.
ركز على واجباتك
Never say
لا تقل أبدا
what shouldn't be said.
ما لا ينبغي أن يقال.
Especially my father's autopsy report,
وخاصة تقرير تشريح جثة والدي،
should it surface,
إذا ظهرت على السطح،
you know the consequences.
أنت تعرف العواقب.
Mr. Gu,
السيد جو،
we just received intel.
لقد تلقينا للتو معلومات استخباراتية.
Last night, Gu Tongpei rushed
الليلة الماضية، هرع غو تونغبي
a critically ill woman to the hospital.
امرأة في حالة حرجة إلى المستشفى.
She might be Miss Chu Minghui.
قد تكون الآنسة تشو مينغهوي.
Take men and follow me to arrest.
خذ الرجال واتبعني للاعتقال.
Understood.
مفهومة.
Over here!
هنا!
Where is the patient in this ward?
أين المريض في هذا الجناح؟
She was here just moments ago.
لقد كانت هنا منذ لحظات.
She is a wanted fugitive.
إنها هاربة مطلوبة.
Urgently notify
إبلاغ عاجلا
the hospital staff to search thoroughly.
يطلب من موظفي المستشفى إجراء بحث شامل.
Hurry!
عجل!
The bed is still warm,
السرير لا يزال دافئا
so she can't have left long.
لذا لا يمكن أن تكون قد غادرت لفترة طويلة.
Search!
يبحث!
Understood!
مفهوم!
Go.
يذهب.
Mr. Gu,
السيد جو،
in such a state,
في مثل هذه الحالة،
she can't swallow any medicine.
لا يمكنها أن تبتلع أي دواء.
Mind your own business.
اهتم بشؤونك الخاصة.
Get out!
اخرج!
Why won't you just leave me alone?
لماذا لا تتركني وحدي؟
Why must I suffer this torment alive?
لماذا يجب أن أعاني هذا العذاب وأنا على قيد الحياة؟
Chu Minghui,
تشو مينغوي,
you must not die.
لا يجب أن تموت.
Don't leave without any explanation,
لا تغادر دون أي تفسير،
making me suffer alone.
جعلني أعاني وحدي.
Drink the medicine.
اشرب الدواء
Is there nothing
هل هناك شيء
in this world
في هذا العالم
worth your attachment?
هل يستحق ارتباطك به؟
No. I want you to stay away from me.
لا أريدك أن تبتعد عني.
If you wish to escape, recover quickly.
إذا كنت تريد الهروب، تعافى بسرعة.
Only then can you leave.
حينها فقط يمكنك المغادرة.
I refuse!
انا ارفض!
Chu Minghui.
تشو مينغوي.
What's all this racket?
ما كل هذا الضجيج؟
Ever since you moved in,
منذ أن انتقلت إلى هنا،
you've kept making noises.
لقد واصلت إصدار الضوضاء.
No one here gets a decent sleep.
لا أحد هنا يحظى بنوم لائق.
Move aside!
تنحى جانبا!
Move aside now!
تنحى جانبا الآن!
Don't you dare die here!
لا تجرؤ على الموت هنا!
Otherwise, nobody would ever rent my place.
وإلا فلن يستأجر أحد المكان الخاص بي أبدًا.
Death solves everything for you,
الموت يحل لك كل شيء
but I've got mouths to feed!
ولكن لدي أفواهًا لأطعمها!
If you dare bring us trouble,
إذا تجرأت على جلب المتاعب لنا،
I'll hunt you down even in the afterlife!
سأطاردك حتى في الحياة الآخرة!
I'm about to become a mother,
أنا على وشك أن أصبح أمًا،
so I can't stand seeing you treat yourself like this.
لذلك لا أستطيع أن أتحمل رؤيتك تعامل نفسك بهذه الطريقة.
Your mother has raised you.
لقد ربتك والدتك.
If she knew your current state,
لو كانت تعرف حالتك الحالية،
how heartbroken she'd be!
كم سيكون قلبها محطما!
Though I'm carrying this baby,
على الرغم من أنني أحمل هذا الطفل،
she's never made things difficult.
إنها لم تجعل الأمور صعبة أبدًا.
She knows how exhausting it is for me all alone.
إنها تعلم مدى الإرهاق الذي أشعر به عندما أكون وحدي.
Yet at your age, you're not as thoughtful as her!
ولكن في سنك، أنت لست متفكراً مثلها!
All you do will make your mother worry.
كل ما تفعله سيجعل والدتك تقلق.
Now drink your medicine!
الآن اشرب الدواء الخاص بك!
Gu Tongpei, Chu Minghui,
قو تونغبي، تشو مينغوي،
someday I'll make you repay double
في يوم من الأيام سأجعلك ترد الجميل مضاعفًا
for the pain I've suffered today.
للألم الذي عانيت منه اليوم.
♪Love is an abyss one cannot escape♪
♪الحب هو الهاوية التي لا يمكن الهروب منها♪
♪The more I doubt, the more I fear♪
كلما زاد شكي، زاد خوفي
♪Sparks of hatred ignite within the heart♪
♪تشتعل شرارات الكراهية في القلب♪
♪The more I struggle, the hoarser my voice becomes♪
كلما كافحت أكثر، أصبح صوتي أكثر خشونة
♪I guard myself over and over again♪
♪أحمي نفسي مرارا وتكرارا♪
♪I hesitate in every word and every moment♪
♪أتردد في كل كلمة وفي كل لحظة♪
♪I feign, struggle♪
♪أتظاهر، أكافح♪
♪Flee, and break♪
♪اهرب وانكسر♪
♪The endless shackle of darkness♪
♪قيد الظلام الذي لا نهاية له♪
♪Let the hatred go♪
♪اترك الكراهية تذهب♪
♪Don't dwell♪
♪لا تتوقف♪
♪Only when flowers wither will scars form♪
♪فقط عندما تذبل الزهور تتشكل الندوب♪
♪Let love and hate scatter with the wind♪
♪دع الحب والكراهية يتناثران مع الريح♪
♪Let myself be free♪
♪أسمح لنفسي أن أكون حرا♪